<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>

  <data>

    <record id="demo_journal_categ_1" model="ojm.journal.category">
      <field name="name">Theoritical Science</field>
      <field name="description">
        This category includes science that focus on theory first.
      </field>
      <field name="sequence">1</field>
    </record>

    <record id="demo_journal_categ_2" model="ojm.journal.category">
      <field name="name">Pratical Science</field>
      <field name="description">
        This category includes science that focus on application/practice first.
      </field>
      <field name="sequence">2</field>
    </record>      

    <record id="demo_journal_1" model="ojm.journal">
      <field name="name">Natural Mathematics</field>
      <field name="logo" type="base64" file="ojm/static/src/img/demo/journal_logo.png"/>
      <field name="cover" type="base64" file="ojm/static/src/img/demo/journal_cover.png"/>
      <field name="description">
        <![CDATA[
          <p>
            Natural Mathematics is an international, peer-reviewed open-access journal 
            dedicated to exploring the profound connections between mathematics and the 
            natural world. The journal provides a platform for original research, reviews, 
            and methodological advances that highlight how mathematical theory, modeling, 
            and computation contribute to understanding natural phenomena.
          </p>
          <p>
            The scope of Natural Mathematics includes, but is not limited to:
            <ul>
              <li>Mathematical biology and ecology</li>
              <li>Dynamical systems in physics and chemistry</li>
              <li>Biostatistics and epidemiological modeling</li>
              <li>Mathematical approaches to earth and environmental sciences</li>
              <li>Computational and data-driven methods for natural processes</li>
              <li>Applied mathematics for sustainability and climate change</li>
            </ul>
          </p>
          <p>
            By fostering interdisciplinary dialogue, the journal seeks to bridge the gap between 
            abstract mathematics and real-world applications, promoting discoveries that advance 
            both theoretical insight and practical solutions.
          </p>
          <p>
            Published quarterly, Natural Mathematics welcomes contributions from mathematicians, 
            scientists, and practitioners worldwide who are committed to expanding the role of 
            mathematics in interpreting and solving natural challenges.
          </p>
        ]]>
      </field>
      <field name="brief_description">
        Natural Mathematics is an international, peer-reviewed journal exploring the interplay 
        between mathematics and the natural world. It publishes original research, reviews, and 
        methodological advances in areas such as mathematical biology, ecology, physics, and 
        environmental sciences. The journal emphasizes the use of mathematical models, computation, 
        and data-driven methods to explain natural phenomena. By fostering interdisciplinary dialogue, 
        it bridges abstract mathematics with real-world applications. Natural Mathematics is published 
        quarterly and welcomes contributions from researchers worldwide.
      </field>
      <field name="mission_scope" >
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>Mission</h2>
          <p>
            The mission of Natural Mathematics is to advance understanding of the natural world 
            through the power of mathematics. The journal strives to provide a platform where 
            theoretical innovation meets practical application, fostering research that bridges 
            pure mathematics with real-world scientific challenges. By encouraging interdisciplinary 
            collaboration, it seeks to inspire solutions that contribute to scientific progress 
            and societal well-being.
          </p>
          <h2>Scope</h2>
          <p>
            Natural Mathematics welcomes high-quality contributions in areas where mathematics 
            illuminates natural processes, including but not limited to:
            <ul>
              <li>Mathematical biology, ecology, and epidemiology</li>
              <li>Dynamical systems in physics, chemistry, and earth sciences</li>
              <li>Computational models and data-driven approaches</li>
              <li>Climate change, sustainability, and environmental modeling</li>
              <li>Applied statistics and quantitative methodologies in natural sciences</li>
            </ul>
          </p>
          <p>
            The journal is committed to publishing work that demonstrates both mathematical rigor 
            and relevance to pressing natural and scientific questions.
          </p>
        ]]>
      </field>
      <field name="editorial_policies" >
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>Editorial Policies</h2>
          <h3>Peer Review</h3>
          <p>
          All manuscripts submitted to Natural Mathematics undergo a rigorous peer-review process. 
          Submissions are first evaluated by the editorial team for scope, originality, and quality. 
          Suitable manuscripts are then reviewed by at least two independent experts to ensure 
          scientific validity, clarity, and relevance.
          </p>
          <h3>Open Access</h3>
          <p>
          The journal is committed to open access, ensuring that published research is freely available 
          to the global community without subscription or access barriers.
          </p>
          <h3>Ethical Standards</h3>
          <p>
          Authors must adhere to the highest standards of academic integrity. Plagiarism, data 
          fabrication, and duplicate submissions are strictly prohibited. The journal follows 
          internationally recognized ethical guidelines, including COPE (Committee on Publication 
          Ethics) principles.
          </p>
          <h3>Authorship & Contributions</h3>
          <p>
          All listed authors must have made a significant contribution to the research and approved 
          the final version of the manuscript. Any conflicts of interest must be disclosed at submission.
          </p>
          <h3>Data & Transparency</h3>
          <p>
          Authors are encouraged to share data, models, and code to support reproducibility and transparency. 
          Supplementary materials may be published alongside articles when appropriate.
          </p>
          <h3>Corrections & Retractions</h3>
          <p>
          In cases of major errors or ethical breaches, the journal reserves the right to issue corrections, 
          expressions of concern, or retractions in line with best publishing practices.
          </p>
        ]]>
      </field>
      <field name="inff_author" >
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>Information for Authors</h2>
          <h3>Manuscript Submission</h3>
          <p>
          Authors are invited to submit original research articles, reviews, or methodological papers relevant 
          to the journal’s scope. Submissions must be made electronically through the online submission system.
          </p>
          <h3>Formatting Guidelines</h3>
          <p>
          Manuscripts should be written in clear English. <br/>
          Use standard structure: Title, Abstract, Keywords, Introduction, Methods, Results, Discussion, References.<br/>
          Figures and tables must be high quality and properly labeled.<br/>
          References should follow a consistent citation style (APA, IEEE, or as specified in the submission portal).<br/>
          <h3>Open Access Policy</h3>
          <p>
          All articles are published under open access, ensuring free and permanent availability to the global research community.
          </p>
          <h3>Ethical Requirements</h3>
          <p>
          Authors must ensure originality of their work, cite relevant sources, and avoid plagiarism. 
          Studies involving human or animal subjects must include ethical approval statements.
          </p>
          <h3>Review Process</h3>
          <p>
          Each manuscript will undergo an initial editorial screening followed by double-blind peer review. 
          Decisions (accept, revise, reject) will be communicated promptly.
          </p>
          <h3>Article Charges</h3>
          <p>
          As an open-access journal, publication may involve article processing charges (APCs). 
          Waivers or discounts may be available for authors from low- and middle-income countries.
          </p>
          <h3>Copyright & Licensing</h3>
          <p>
          Authors retain copyright under a Creative Commons license, allowing wide dissemination 
          and reuse with proper attribution.
          </p>
          <h3>Contact</h3>
          <p>
          For inquiries regarding submission, formatting, or policies, authors may contact the 
          editorial office at: editor@naturalmathjournal.org
          </p>
        ]]>
      </field>
      <field name="inff_reviewer" >
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>Information for Reviewers</h2>
          <h3>Role of Reviewers</h3>
          <p>
          Reviewers play a critical role in maintaining the quality, integrity, and credibility 
          of Natural Mathematics. Their evaluations ensure that published manuscripts meet the 
          highest standards of originality, clarity, and scientific rigor.
          </p>
          <h3>Review Process</h3>
          <p>
          Reviews are conducted under a double-blind policy: both authors and reviewers remain anonymous.
          Reviewers are expected to provide constructive, objective, and timely feedback.
          The typical review period is 2–4 weeks from the date of invitation.
          </p>
          <h3>Evaluation Criteria</h3>
          <p>
          Reviewers should assess:
          <ul>
            <li>Relevance of the manuscript to the journal’s scope.</li>
            <li>Originality and significance of the contribution.</li>
            <li>Soundness of methodology and analysis.</li>
            <li>Clarity of presentation and structure.</li>
            <li>Proper referencing of prior work.</li>
            <li>Ethical Responsibilities</li>
            <li>Maintain confidentiality of all submitted material.</li>
            <li>Declare any conflicts of interest before accepting a review.</li>
            <li>Avoid using or sharing unpublished data for personal advantage.</li>
          </ul>
          </p>
          <h3>Recognition</h3>
          <p>
          Reviewers’ contributions are acknowledged through annual certificates of service, and exceptional 
          reviewers may be highlighted by the editorial board.
          </p>
          <h3>Support</h3>
          <p>
          Guidelines and reviewer resources are available on the journal’s website. For questions, 
          contact: review@naturalmathjournal.org
          </p>
        ]]>
      </field>
      <!-- <field name="journal_metrics"></field>
      <field name="journal_contact"></field> -->
      <field name="active">1</field>
      <field name="is_published">1</field>
      <field name="sequence">1</field>
      <field name="category_id" ref="ojm.demo_journal_categ_1"/>
    </record>

    <record id="editor_position_1" model="ojm.editor.position">
      <field name="name">Chief Editor</field>
    </record>

    <record id="editor_position_2" model="ojm.editor.position">
      <field name="name">Associate Editor</field>
    </record>

  </data>

</odoo>