<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <data noupdate="1">
    
        <record id="article_type_1" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Research Article</field>
            <field name="description">Research articles present original and significant research findings in a specific field.
            They typically include sections such as Introduction, Methods, Results, and Discussion, and contribute to
            the advancement of knowledge in the given area.</field>
            <field name="sequence">1</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_2" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Review Article</field>
            <field name="description">Review articles provide a comprehensive overview of existing research literature on a
            specific topic. They summarize, analyze, and synthesize information from multiple sources to present a
            balanced and thorough understanding of the subject.</field>
            <field name="sequence">2</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_3" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Case Study</field>
            <field name="description">Case studies offer an in-depth analysis of a particular instance, situation, or event. 
            They often explore real-world scenarios, providing insights, lessons learned, and implications for a broader context.</field>
            <field name="sequence">3</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_4" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Opinion Pieces</field>
            <field name="description">Opinion pieces allow authors to express their viewpoints, perspectives, or 
            insights on a particular topic. While they may be based on personal experiences or observations, 
            they should still be well-argued and informed.</field>
            <field name="sequence">4</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_5" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Letter to the Editor</field>
            <field name="description">Letters to the Editor are brief communications that comment on, critique, or discuss
            content previously published in the journal. They provide an opportunity for scholarly discourse and
            reader engagement</field>
            <field name="sequence">5</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_6" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Collection Review &amp; Overview</field>
            <field name="description">This type involves reviewing and providing an overview of a collection of
            research articles or works related to a specific theme or subject advertised by the journal you are
            submitting your manuscript to. Please do not select this option unless you have been instructed to do so
            by the journal.</field>
            <field name="sequence">6</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>

        <record id="article_type_7" model="ojm.article.type">
            <field name="name">Others</field>
            <field name="description">If your manuscript does not fit into the predefined categories, please select this option.
            However, ensure that you provide a clear description of the article type in the relevant fields. Select the most 
            suitable option that aligns with your manuscript's content. Make sure your submission follows the guidelines 
            outlined for the chosen article type. Should you have any inquiries or require further clarification, 
            please consult our guidelines or reach out to our editorial team for assistance.</field>
            <field name="sequence">7</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
        </record>
    
    </data>
    

</odoo>
