<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">
        <record id="remind_reviewer_email_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Email: Remind Reviewer</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="ojm.model_ojm_reviewer_assignment"/>
            <field name="email_from"></field>
            <field name="email_to">{{object.reviewer_email}}</field>
            <field name="subject">Sayans Gentle Reminder: Review Invitation for Manuscript {{object.article_id.code}}</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div>
                    <p>
                        Dear <t t-out="object.reviewer_id.name"/>,
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        We hope this email finds you well. We are writing to gently remind you about
                        the pending review of the manuscript titled "<t t-out="object.article_id.short_title"/>"
                        for <t t-out="object.article_id.journal_id.name"/>.
                        Thank you once again for accepting our invitation to review this submission.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        As you know, your expertise is invaluable to ensuring the quality
                        and credibility of the peer review process. Your insights and feedback are eagerly
                        anticipated by both the authors and the editorial team.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        If you have already begun the review process, we sincerely appreciate your efforts
                        and encourage you to submit your feedback at your earliest convenience. If you have
                        not yet had the opportunity to commence the review, we kindly ask you to prioritize
                        it in your schedule.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        We understand the demands on your time and are grateful for your commitment
                        to advancing scholarly discourse in our field. Your thorough and thoughtful
                        evaluation will significantly contribute to the enhancement of the manuscript
                        and the overall quality of our publication.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        If you foresee any challenges or delays in completing the review by the agreed-upon deadline,
                        please do not hesitate to inform us as soon as possible. We are more than willing to accommodate
                        reasonable extensions to ensure a comprehensive and fair assessment.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Thank you once again for your dedication to scholarly peer review. Your continued support
                        is instrumental in maintaining the high standards of excellence associated with
                        <t t-out="object.article_id.journal_id.name"/>.
                    </p>

                    <hr style="margin-top:3em"/>

                    <p style="font-size:0.75rem">
                        Warm regards,<br/>
                        <b><t t-out="object.article_id.journal_id.name"/></b>  <br/>
                        Sayans Publishers LLP  <br/>
                        00100-Nairobi, Kenya <br/>
                        BN: 2RCYZLDL<br/>
                        Contact: sayanspublishers@sayansi.org<br/>
                        <a href="www.sayansi.org">www.sayansi.org</a>
                    </p>
                </div>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>
